iquitsugar.com 2018-06-04

# I Quit Sugar Privacy Policy - I Quit Sugar

* **Introduction**

Welcome to the Privacy Policy for IQuitSugar.com (“Site”) and any associated services owned by I Quit Sugar Pty Ltd. Throughout this policy, the words “IQS”, “us”, “we” and “our” refer to our company, I Quit Sugar Pty Ltd and our Site or any “Services” we provide, as is appropriate in the context of the use of the words.

We recognised the importance of protecting the privacy of individuals and their personal information. We aim to provide a Site and Services that will ensure the information you provide to us online is collected, managed and disclosed in a secure and confidential manner.

We’ve tried to make our Privacy Policy easy to understand so that you are informed as to how we use your information. This Privacy Policy, like our [Terms of Service and Conditions](https://iquitsugar.com/terms-and-conditions/), is an integral part of using our Services; therefore you must completely agree to our Privacy Policy in order to use our Site or Services. You must be over the age of 18 to use our Site or Services, or a minimum 13 years of age with a parent’s permission. You must be 18 years of age or older to purchase any products or Services from IQS.

* **Information collected**

_Personally identifiable information submitted by you_

You will not be required to provide us with any information when you visit our Site. However, if you opt to receive email communications from us (such as the I Quit Sugar Weekly newsletter) we will ask you for your name, email address and a little bit about you, such as what country you live in. 

In order to purchase any products, you could be required to submit your name, email, address, phone contact and payment information.

If you wish to sign up for any Programs, you may also be asked to submit additional information including, but not limited to, your address, mobile number, physical characteristics and your health goals.

Please be aware that all payment information will be shared with and stored by our third-party payment processor, Paypal.

_Non-identifying information_

Whenever you use our Site or Services, we may collect non-identifying information from you, such as your IP address, interactions with the Site and Services, query information, location, referring URL, browser, operating system, cookie information, usage, data transferred, and Internet Service Provider. Without a subpoena, voluntary compliance on the part of your Internet Service Provider or additional records from a third party, such as your wireless provider, this information alone cannot usually be used to identify you.

* **Use of your information**

We will never sell or transfer any personally identifiable information to third parties without your consent. However, you agree that we may use your information to:

  * enhance or improve our users’ experiences.
  * provide our Services to you.
  * email you newsletters and correspondence.
  * process your transactions.
  * contact you and to respond to inquiries.

Additionally, we may give your information to law enforcement if we are compelled to by a court order, if there has been a violation of any laws or if a violation of the Terms of Service or Privacy Policy has occurred.

* **Accessing, editing and removing your information**

You will not be able to access any information submitted to our Site. However, if you have any questions or wish to review, change or delete any of your information submitted, please contact us at [info@iquitsugar.com](mailto:info@iquitsugar.com). Additionally, if you wish to opt out of our data collection practices or would like us to remove any of your information, please contact us at [info@iquitsugar.com](mailto:info@iquitsugar.com). After you have you have submitted information to us, please be aware that we may keep inaccessible copies of your information for a commercially reasonable period of time.

* **Cookies and tracking**

_Cookies_

We use cookies on our Site and Services. Cookies are little bits of code that help us determine your preferences and allow us to track your advertisements. Additionally, some or all of our cookies may be accessible by third parties to help improve your experience. For this reason we ask that you have cookies enabled while using our Site or Services.

_Google Analytics and Google Adwords_

We use Google Analytics. This is a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”), whereby website traffic and usage data is transmitted to and stored by Google in the U.S. Google uses this information to evaluate website usages and provide us with reports that help us understand website traffic and usage. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data it holds. By using our site you consent to the processing of data about you by Google as described in Google’s Privacy Policy. 

We also use Google AdWords and remarketing to display specific advertisements to visitors that have previously visited our site when those visitors go to other websites that have the Google Display network implemented. Along with other third-party vendors, including Google, we use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) to display these ads.

When creating remarketing lists, we can’t and don’t use any sensitive information about users. As AdWords advertisers, we are restricted from and will not perform the following actions:

  1. Running ads that collect Personally Identifiable Information (PII) including, but not limited to, email addresses, telephone numbers and credit card numbers. 
  2. Creating a remarketing list or creating ad text that specifically targets users in ways that are outlined as “prohibited”.

You can opt out of Google Analytics for display advertising and customise Google Display ads using the Ads Preferences Manager by visiting www.google.com/settings/ads.

_Kissmetrics_

We use Kissmetrics. This is a web analytics service provided by Space Pencil, Inc. Kissmetrics only uses first-party cookies for identifying users. This information is cleared when you clear your browser cookies. You can opt out using the opt-out link at the Kissmetrics website: <http://www.kissmetrics.com/user-privacy>.

_Social interfaces_

We also use interfaces with social media including Facebook and Twitter. If you “like” or “share” information from our site via these services, we recommend reviewing their privacy policies. If you are a member of Facebook or Twitter, the interfaces may allow the them to connect your visits with our site with other personal information.

* **Third-party access to your information**

Although you are entering into an Agreement with IQS to disclose your information to us, we do use third-party individuals and organisations to assist us, including contractors, web hosts and others.

In providing our Services to you, we may delegate our authority to collect, access, use and distribute your information. In agreeing to this Privacy Policy you agree that every authorisation you grant to us under this Privacy Policy is also granted to any third party that we may hire, contract or otherwise retain the services of in operating, maintaining, repairing, improving or preserving our Site and Services. You agree not to hold us liable for the actions of any of these third parties, even if we would normally be held vicariously liable for their actions, and that you must take legal action against them directly should they commit any actionable wrong against you. 

The following is a non-exhaustive list of other entities that we may store, share or transfer your information with:

  * AdSense
  * MailChimp
  * ZenDesk
  * PayPal
  * Bigcommerce
  * Infusionsoft
  * Kissmetrics
  * Braintree Payments
  * WP Engine
  * Amazon Web Services

* **Law enforcement**

You agree that we may disclose your information to authorities if compelled to by a court order. Additionally, you agree that we may disclose your information if we reasonably believe that you have violated the law or the terms of our Terms of Service or Privacy Policy, or if we believe that a third party is at risk of bodily harm.

In the event that we receive a subpoena affecting your privacy, we may elect to notify you to give you an opportunity to file a motion to quash the subpoena, or we may attempt to quash it ourselves, but we are not obligated to do either. We may also proactively report you and release your information without receiving any request to third parties where we believe that it is proper to do so for legal reasons, such as instances where we believe your publications violate any Australian laws or any other country having jurisdiction over us, our Site, Services or our Terms of Service.

You release us from any damages that may arise from or relate to the release of your information to a request from law enforcement agencies or private litigants. We may release your information under the conditions listed in this paragraph whether it is to individuals or entities and to any state or national authorities, as required.

* **Commercial and non-commercial communications**

If you decide to provide us with your contact information, you waive all rights to file complaints concerning unsolicited emails from us, since you have agreed to such communication. However, you may unsubscribe from certain communications by notifying IQS that you no longer wish to receive these solicitations, and we will endeavour to remove you from our database where you have the right to request this under our Agreement, Privacy Policy or applicable law. If you wish to opt out of certain communications, please contact us at [info@iquitsugar.com](mailto:info@iquitsugar.com).

* **Third parties**

IQS may post links to third party websites on our Site or Services, which may include information that we have no control over. When accessing a third party site through our Site or Services, you acknowledge that you are aware that these third-party websites are not screened for privacy or security issues by us, and you release us from any liability for the conduct of these third-party websites.

Please be aware that this Privacy Policy, and any other policies in place, in addition to any amendments, does not create rights enforceable by third parties. IQS bears no responsibility for the information collected or used by any advertiser or third-party website. You must review their Terms of Service and Privacy to understand how their information collection practices work.

* **Security measures**

We take reasonable attempts to protect your information. However, as this is the internet, we can make no guarantees as to the security or privacy of your information. For this reason, we recommend that you use anti-virus software, routine credit checks, firewalls and other precautions to protect yourself from security and privacy threats.

* **Your Australian privacy rights**

IQS intends to comply with 1988 Privacy Act of Australia. If you are an Australian citizen you may wish to ask us additional questions regarding the information we collect. Although we do not disseminate your information to third parties without permission, you must presume that we collect electronic information from all visitors. You may contact us at [info@iquitsugar.com](mailto:info@iquitsugar.com) with any questions.

* **Age compliance**

We intend to fully comply with international laws respecting children’s privacy. Therefore, we do not collect or process any information for any persons under the age of 18. If you are under 18, please do not submit any information to us without parental consent. If you believe that someone under the age of 18 has submitted information to us without parental consent, please contact us immediately.

* **International transfer**

Your information may be transferred to – and maintained on – computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction, where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. We may transfer personal information to Australia or elsewhere and process it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy, followed by your submission of such information, represents your agreement to that transfer.

* **Amendments**

Like our Terms of Service, we may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we amend this Privacy Policy, we will modify the date listed on this Agreement or we may contact you. You must agree to the amendments as a condition of your continued use of our Site and Services. If you do not agree, you must immediately cease using our Site and Services, and notify us of your refusal to agree by emailing us at [info@iquitsugar.com](mailto:info@iquitsugar.com).
